[ED.
Yes, so this time, we at Grail have put together our own coding! How did you like it?
What did you think?
There were so many cute ones.
There were so many!
I think we made some pretty cute outfits.
It was pretty much a total outfit, wasn't it?
And I thought, "I'm not doing this for other people, I'm doing this for myself.
I wondered how I should make it look like.
But I think it turned out to be a very Kira-like look.
I think it turned out that way.
Now, I'd like to introduce the items I purchased. What's the name of Yoko's top? I'm not sure what to call this one from Shiro.
It's a frilly off-the-shoulder kind of thing, and it's right here.
This is the item that's been getting a lot of buzz in gray, and the most popular color is probably charcoal.
The grayish one was probably the most popular, but when I was trying to coordinate with various outfits today, I wanted something that had a little bit of a "Nen-asai" feel to it.
I chose white, and I'm the complete opposite, pitch black.
I chose a one-piece dress so that I could wear it alone rather than as a top. It's black, but there's a string at the shoulder to show some skin, so I decided to make it a one-piece in order to give it a cooler look.
It's black, right?
The bottoms are simple jeans. Here they are.
The model wearing them had a really beautiful silhouette, so I was really attracted to them, and there were a lot of different kinds of jeans, but I decided on these.
I was really attracted by the silhouette of the model wearing them, and there were a lot of different kinds of jeans, but these are the ones I chose.
I really like this one, too.
I have a lot of clothes and accessories like this.
I'm going to start with the hair accessory, which is a ribbon from Kowtow.
But I made a mistake... putting it in a bun today.
But I was really attracted to this baby pink-ish color, so I chose it.
I wanted to unify the bag as well. I wanted something a little more subdued and similar to this color, but it was sold out.
I wanted something a little more subdued and similar to this color, but it was sold out, so when I looked for something similar, I found this one and chose it because it had a cute shape.
The quilted back is cute.
These are pearl heeled sandals.
They're clear, and they're full of pearls, so they're very natural.
I chose these because they are so cute!
I'm looking forward to seeing how they look when I wear them. I'm wearing a black dress, so I thought I'd add a little color here to make it look cute.
I chose this pink bag to add a little color and cuteness to my black dress, and I also chose this pink bag.
The sun has been shining lately, so I decided to add a little summery touch with this bag.
I don't like to show my toes.I guess you could call it a fingertip.
So I decided to go with gold accessories.
The pink bag is also a matching item. We chose pink because we wanted to bring out the cuteness.
I thought pink was the perfect color for summer to make it look cute. Now that we've introduced our items, we'd like to get dressed up!
Let's go to 3:00 p.m.!
It's 3:00 p.m.
none
So here we are!
How do you like it? Try it on. It's cute. It looks really good on you. It's nice. It's totally different. It's totally different.
This is a bit, well, a bit of a failure, isn't it? Yes. Actually, it would be cute to wear it half-up like this, but I think it's not quite right.
I don't know. I guess so. It's totally cute. A little bit. I'm sure. I thought it would be nice if I could wear it. Yes, it would be. We both wear different kinds of clothes, so depending on the occasion, we would be happy if you could imitate our clothes. Yes. What do you think?
Well, the fabric is much more solid than I expected, and it looks very expensive. It's easy to pick up. It's easy to pick up. It's very comfortable to wear. And the price is not that expensive. It's amazing. How about the shoes?
Shoes, you know, like this. See? They look pretty good. I'm easy to walk in. They are easy to walk in. I like shoes with heels, but they're pretty stable. Me too. See? It's nice. Looks cool. Yes, it does. It looks really cool. It's refreshing, clean, and cute. Cute.
This one looks like this, too, but you can lift it up. Oh, wow. Like this. I see. You can also wear it like this. But I think it looks cuter with it out. My shoulders are a little too broad, a little Gundam-like. No, it's not like that. A little bit. So I think this one fits me better, so I wear this one.
I have beautiful collarbones. I have beautiful collarbones, so the official look suits me very well. I'm happy. It's nice. What do you think? What do you think of our coordination?
Is that what you mean?
Yes. So, I did an introduction of the items purchased by Grail. Thank you for watching. Thank you very much. If you like this video, please give it a high rating, subscribe to our channel, and comment. Thank you very much. Bye bye.